constant-content.com 2018-05-12

# Privacy Policy - Constant-Content.com

Constant-Content Media Company

This statement sets out the privacy practices and policies of Revenuwire Inc. (“Constant-Content”) in relation to any information that you may share with Constant-Content.

Constant-Content reserves the right to update this policy from time to time, on reasonable notice to you. Your continued use of any website or service covered by this policy after we have notified you of an amendment will constitute your agreement to the same.

In this statement, when we talk about “Constant-Content” or “we” or “our”, we are referring to Constant-Content Media Company, and its majority-owned or controlled subsidiaries.

### 1\. Personal Information

In connection with your use, from time to time, of the Constant-Content website or service, you may be required to provide Constant-Content with certain personal information, including without limitation, your name, address, telephone number, electronic mail addresss, credit card information, bank account information, and your social insurance or social security number (collectively, your “Personal Information”).

Constant-Content will use your Personal Information to establish your account, to communicate with you, to remit payments to you from time to time if and when due, and for ongoing record keeping, as required by law.

Constant-Content will not release Personal Information about you without your permission, except:

  * (a) as permitted in this policy statement; 
  * (b) as permitted in any written agreement between you and Constant-Content; 
  * (c) where we believe it is reasonably necessary to conduct business; and 
  * (d) where we believe it is necessary to enforce our rights under any agreement between you and Constant-Content.

Constant-Content will provide both a means for you to manage and control the information that you have voluntarily provided to us and a means for you to communicate your privacy questions and concerns to us.

We will not knowingly collect Personal Information on users under the age of eighteen. We encourage parents and guardians to monitor the Internet based activities of their children.

### 2\. Anonymous Information

“Anonymous Information” is information other than Personal Information, and includes the domain names, IP addresses and type of browsers that you may use, from time to time, referring URLs, and other, non-personally identifiable information.

When you access any site or service covered by this policy statement, we collect Anonymous Information. We use this information for system administration, to market research (which is shared with our advertisers), to personalize your experience at our site, to show you more relevant advertising messages, and, generally, to improve our services. We share this Anonymous Information with selected advertisers and partners in order to deliver to you more relevant advertising messages.

Constant-Content will not share any Anonymous Information if that information is or will be linked to your Personal Information, unless we have given you notice as described above and you have given us authorization to do so.

Constant-Content can and will use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site’s terms of use or terms of service, or to protect our service, site, or other users.

### 3\. Sharing Personal Information

We will not share your Personal Information unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and you have authorized us to do so. Our partners who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people. In addition, if we add new features or services that might require the sharing of your personal information with other parties, we will provide you with notice and the opportunity to opt-in to receive these offers.

In certain special cases, we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with Constant-Content’s rights, property or operations, other Constant-Content users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

### 4\. Third Party Relationships

Constant-Content has relationships with many of the best media and services companies throughout the world.

Whenever you provide registration information on certain co-branded Web pages or for certain services provided in conjunction with third party partners, some data you provide is shared with partners. You should make every effort to read the privacy policies provided by or in association with such third parties, and make an informed decision on your own whether or not to continue utilizing the services based on the privacy policies posted on these co-branded Web pages, at your own discretion.

In addition to finding co-branded Web pages, you may find direct links to Constant-Content on third party websites. You may also find direct links from third party websites to Constant-Content. Constant-Content cannot guarantee that these sites have adopted acceptable privacy policies. You should read these third party privacy policies, and make an informed decision on your own as to whether or not to continue based on these sites’ privacy practices, at your own discretion. No third party sites are covered by this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Security

Constant-Content operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. Constant-Content has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. Unfortunately, no method of data transmission or storage is entirely secure, and while we make reasonable efforts to protect date stored on our networks, we cannot ensure or warrant that security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on Constant-Content employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort (such as the use of employee passwords and non-disclosure agreements) to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

### 6\. Contacting Us

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, please contact us.

***Constant-Content reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be posted to this page. we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any material changes to this privacy policy.   **

**This privacy policy was modified as of February 23rd, 2010, and is effective as of March 1st, 2010.  
**
